<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>non-fiction on Writing</title>
    <link>/tags/non-fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in non-fiction on Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/non-fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A backwards clock</title>
      <link>/post/a-backwards-clock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-backwards-clock/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a square I visit often. In the center of this square, there&amp;rsquo;s a clock that is made backwards. This clock is not going to the past, although that might be the starting point of a nice fiction piece. It tells the time just the same as a normal clock, that is, it&amp;rsquo;s accurately moving into the future and can be read by anybody who encounters it.
In a normal clock, the seconds hand moves, well, clockwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyone is a Billionaire</title>
      <link>/post/everyone-is-a-billionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/everyone-is-a-billionaire/</guid>
      <description>We are all billionaires. But not in the way you are thinking. Let me clarify using a bit of back-of-the-envelope math. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling optimistic, so I will assume you will live 100 years. Most people average between 60 and 100 heart beats per minute, which turns out to be between 3 and 5 billion beats per human life, give or take. Living shorter means you get less beats, probably closer to 2 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the spiral</title>
      <link>/post/into-the-spiral/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/into-the-spiral/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t yield to the spiral. Don&amp;rsquo;t go there. You know where it goes, you know what your life looks like once you are down in the crater.
Yes, you know the place, you&amp;rsquo;ve flirted with the crater all your life. And you know how to get there. I know because I know exactly what I tell myself. I only need to get a toe wet in the spiral and I will slide into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All you did not choose</title>
      <link>/post/all-you-did-not-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/all-you-did-not-choose/</guid>
      <description>You did not choose your name, not the first one, that one was given to you. You did not choose your country of birth or the soil that you were taught to call home.
You did not choose your face, the weird wrinkle that defines you. You didn&amp;rsquo;t choose your skin tone, nor whatever other people will think about it.
You didn&amp;rsquo;t choose your mother tongue. You didn&amp;rsquo;t choose the way you speak, your vocal cords, your unconscious cadence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All of us</title>
      <link>/post/all-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/all-of-us/</guid>
      <description>They will give you cancer. If you ask, they will lie about it. They will lie about it for 50 years. After that, they will awake to a new consciousness, a fresh peaceful self. They will say they want to stop selling you nicotine packaged with cancer. From now on, they will only sell you nicotine in a different shape, one that is appealing to new generation of kids that were not going to be addicts in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>