<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Writing</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyone is a Billionaire</title>
      <link>/post/everyone-is-a-billionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/everyone-is-a-billionaire/</guid>
      <description>We are all billionaires. But not in the way you are thinking. Let me clarify using a bit of back-of-the-envelope math. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling optimistic, so I will assume you will live 100 years. Most people average between 60 and 100 heart beats per minute, which turns out to be between 3 and 5 billion beats per human life, give or take. Living shorter means you get less beats, probably closer to 2 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the spiral</title>
      <link>/post/into-the-spiral/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/into-the-spiral/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t yield to the spiral. Don&amp;rsquo;t go there. You know where it goes, you know what your life looks like once you are down in the crater.
Yes, you know the place, you&amp;rsquo;ve flirted with the crater all your life. And you know how to get there. I know because I know exactly what I tell myself. I only need to get a toe wet in the spiral and I will slide into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lasik</title>
      <link>/post/lasik/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/lasik/</guid>
      <description>After that thought settled, she realized she would never see the world the same way again. She realized there was no going back after Lasik. Her eyesight was gone forever. The world was pitch black and quiet. She didn&amp;rsquo;t really know where she was, she had the feeling of being seated, though she couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell for sure. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t deaf but the silence was more disturbing than the lack of vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All you did not choose</title>
      <link>/post/all-you-did-not-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/all-you-did-not-choose/</guid>
      <description>You did not choose your name, not the first one, that one was given to you. You did not choose your country of birth or the soil that you were taught to call home.
You did not choose your face, the weird wrinkle that defines you. You didn&amp;rsquo;t choose your skin tone, nor whatever other people will think about it.
You didn&amp;rsquo;t choose your mother tongue. You didn&amp;rsquo;t choose the way you speak, your vocal cords, your unconscious cadence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All of us</title>
      <link>/post/all-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/all-of-us/</guid>
      <description>They will give you cancer. If you ask, they will lie about it. They will lie about it for 50 years. After that, they will awake to a new consciousness, a fresh peaceful self. They will say they want to stop selling you nicotine packaged with cancer. From now on, they will only sell you nicotine in a different shape, one that is appealing to new generation of kids that were not going to be addicts in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Univeristy Bridge</title>
      <link>/post/boston-university-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/boston-university-bridge/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sound and sight.
It&amp;rsquo;s shore and sky.
It&amp;rsquo;s that little push, the one you need to go on.
It&amp;rsquo;s a firework burst. Flame on.
It&amp;rsquo;s the moment of peace when you look afar.
It&amp;rsquo;s the runners and bikers, and those who age in a car.
It&amp;rsquo;s the story of our lives, of million eyes and ears alike.
It&amp;rsquo;s the wills and powers that distress us all.
And the smiles of the youth and the old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To move is to commit</title>
      <link>/post/to-move-is-to-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/to-move-is-to-commit/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 8:23. I could catch the 57 bus in exactly 3 minutes. But, could I make the connection over the bridge?
Dubious. Maybe the B line, 4 minutes away. No, I hate the B line, how I wish it was a real subway. Besides, going for the B means forgoing all other options. She said I was afraid to move somewhere together. It would definitely be cheaper rent. Should I be thinking about rent?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Being a Brain</title>
      <link>/post/on-being-a-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/on-being-a-brain/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s no light inside, there&amp;rsquo;s no sound either. There’s no touching around that could guide you. No smell crawling its way towards you. The surroundings are tasteless. You are trapped in a coffin made of bone, a skull that imprisons you in an eternal bath.
In this bath, it&amp;rsquo;s only you and the signals. So your best option is to sit comfortably and contemplate the myriad of miniature sparks that travel from one side to the other, and back.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>